<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<table version="1.000000" name="Feedback-Table" numRows="10" numCols="5" flags="9" tableType="0">
    <rows>
        <row id="0" name="Lesson 1 - Wrong"/>
        <row id="1" name="Lesson 1 - Right"/>
        <row id="2" name="Lesson 2 - Wrong"/>
        <row id="3" name="Lesson 2 - Right"/>
        <row id="4" name="Lesson 3 - Wrong"/>
        <row id="5" name="Lesson 3 - Right"/>
        <row id="6" name="Lesson 4 - Wrong"/>
        <row id="7" name="Lesson 4 - Right"/>
        <row id="8" name="Lesson 5 - Wrong"/>
        <row id="9" name="Lesson 5 - Right"/>
    </rows>
    <columns>
        <column id="0" name="" type="1" readonly="0">You lost a book! Looking up articles and searching on Google are useful. However\, before you can even begin your research\, you should carefully read your assignment. Highlight topic guidelines\, required length\, and the types of informaiton sources allowed.,Correct! It may sound silly\, but before you can even begin your research\, you should carefully read your assignment. Highlight topic guidelines\, required length\, and the types of informaiton sources allowed.,You lost a book! Many things can make a topic a good choice. It should be something that interests you and is broad enough to give you many search options. At the same time it needs to be focused enough so you are not overwhelmed by thousands of resources.,Correct! Many things can make a topic a good choice. It should be something that interests you and is broad enough to give you many search options. At the same time it needs to be focused enough so you are not overwhelmed by thousands of resources.,Incorrect! You should always start by asking different questions about your chosen topic in order to narrow it. Seeing how some other disciplines may approach it is also helpful.,Good job! You should always start by asking different questions about your chosen topic in order to narrow it. Seeing how some other disciplines may approach it is also helpful.,You lost a book! Newspapers and Magazines provide current information while scholarly journals cover in-depth analyses. Encyclopedias are actually a great general source to get an overview of a topic.,Correct! Newspapers and Magazines provide current information while scholarly journals cover in-depth analyses. Encyclopedias are actually a great general source to get an overview of a topic.,Wrong! Go back to our very first lesson - reading your assignment carefully is the most important thing you can do before beginning research!,Correct! Reading your assignment carefully is the most important thing you can do before beginning research!</column>
        <column id="1" name="" type="1" readonly="0">Incorrect! The key theme or issue is usually in the beginning of the assignment and easier to spot. It is centered around the general topic of the assignment. In this case\, the topic and key theme is &quot;income inequality.&quot;,Good job! The key theme or issue is usually in the beginning of the assignment and easier to spot. It is centered around the general topic of the assignment. In this case\, the topic and key theme is &quot;income inequality.&quot;,Incorrect! This topic is a little too broad. You can narrow it down by exploring speficially families in urban OR rural areas\, for example.,Good job! This topic is a little too broad. You can narrow it down by exploring speficially families in urban OR rural areas\, for example.,Close! Income inequality is obviously a key phrase\, but URBAN AREAS is the phrase that focuses the topic question.,Correct! Income inequality is obviously a key phrase\, but URBAN AREAS is the phrase that focuses the topic question.,Wrong! Encyclopedias will give you an overview of a topic\, but if you are already somewhat familiar with it\, you should look at some books available. Scholarly journals may be too in-depth for you at this point.,Great job! Encyclopedias will give you an overview of a topic\, but if you are already somewhat familiar with it\, you should look at some books available. Scholarly journals may be too in-depth for you at this point.,You lost a book! Of these three\, you definitely want the topic to be interesting to you. If it is too narrow or too broad that you find thousands of articles about it - it may be hard to write a good paper on it.,Great work! Of these three\, you definitely want the topic to be interesting to you. If it is too narrow or too broad that you find thousands of articles about it - it may be hard to write a good paper on it.</column>
        <column id="2" name="" type="1" readonly="0">You lost a book! It is usually easy to spot what your teacher wants you to do - just look for the verbs. In this case\, you need to EXPLORE\, EXAMINE\, and DISCUSS income inequality in the United States.,Correct! It is usually easy to spot what your teacher wants you to do - just look for the verbs. In this case\, you need to EXPLORE\, EXAMINE\, and DISCUSS income inequality in the United States.,You lost a book! This topic is actually just right and you should be able to find some good resources on it.,Tow points! This topic is just right and you should be able to find some good resources on it.,Almost there! There are many synonyms for income inequality\, but perhaps one of the most widely used is &quot;income disparity.&quot;,You know your synonyms! There are many synonyms for income inequality\, but perhaps one of the most widely used is &quot;income disparity.&quot;,Incorrect! Out of the three\, government publications provide the most in-depth research and analyses about a topic.,Correct! Out of the three\, government publications provide the most in-depth research and analyses about a topic.,Wrong! This topic is very broad and can be look at from quite a few angles.,Correct! This topic is very broad and can be look at from quite a few angles.</column>
        <column id="3" name="" type="1" readonly="0">Oh no\, you lost a book! This one is the easiest to find. Just look for any numbers of sources or pages your teacher has asked for - these will be requirements your paper should fulfil. In this case - &quot;three to five authoritative sources.&quot;,Correct! This one is the easiest to find. Just look for any numbers of sources or pages your teacher has asked for - these will be requirements your paper should fulfil. In this case\, &quot;three to five authoritative sources.&quot;,Incorrect! This topic is a little too narrow and there may not be enough research or resources about it.,Correct! This topic is a little too narrow and there may not be enough research or resources about it.,Incorrect! While all of these will give you results\, &quot;urban poor&quot; AND &quot;social conditions&quot; will bring more focused sources to your attention.,Wow\, good job! While all of these will give you results\, &quot;urban poor&quot; AND &quot;social conditions&quot; will bring more focused sources to your attention.,You lost a book! This one should be easy. Newspapers and magazines are the only sources likely to provide current or regional information on a topic.,Two points! This one should be easy. Newspapers and magazines are the only sources likely to provide current or regional information on a topic.,Incorrect! Tailoring to the assignment requirements is a must and talking to a librarian can save you many hours of fruitless searching on the web.,Good job! Tailoring to the assignment requirements is a must and talking to a librarian can save you many hours of fruitless searching on the web.</column>
        <column id="4" name="" type="1" readonly="0">Incorrect! Finding articles and starting to write come a little after you&apos;ve actually picked a narrower topic to write about.,Good work! Finding articles and starting to write come a little after you&apos;ve actually picked a narrower topic to write about.,Incorrect! This one is hard. It is generally a little broad\, however\, since there may not be enough good SCHOLARLY research on this aspect yet.,You are awesome! This one is hard. It is generally a little broad\, however\, since there may not be enough good SCHOLARLY research on this aspect yet.,Wrong! This one is tough. &quot;Income disparity&quot; and cities will give you the best results for exploring income inequality in URBAN areas.,Great work! This one is tough. &quot;Income disparity&quot; and cities will give you the best results for exploring income inequality in URBAN areas.,Almost! This one is harder. Encyclopedia offer factual information\, books serve as good summaries of what is known about a topic\, and sholarly articles provide very detailed analysis of a complex problem.,Great work! This one is harder. Encyclopedia offer factual information\, books serve as good summaries of what is known about a topic\, and sholarly articles provide very detailed analysis of a complex problem.,You lost a book! Article databases are quite sophisticated\, but try to give you only specific results to your search terms. Using different words will help you broaden your search. It won&apos;t narrow your topic though.,Great work! Article databases are quite sophisticated\, but try to give you only specific results to your search terms. Using different words will help you broaden your search. It won&apos;t narrow your topic though.</column>
    </columns>
</table>
